[Music]
Hi, I am Joby from Power Link.
At least once in our lives, we all have
When a hospital case arises
We will have a lot of uncertainty.
But we have a good insurance policy.
If there is, give them all to us.
I can do it, so I always do it.
As you say, you are all one
Must have health insurance
Today I have come to the ICC.
An insurance called Lebard's Elite
Plan
To talk about. Its
Benefits and its features
What it contains
This video will tell you clearly.
Likewise, the mother who starts this video
I will say one thing, that I
We always say which
Company insurance and which company?
Even if we make a plan, we will be honest.
Correct Company for our illnesses
Must be informed. So we don't do that.
If we sit down, maybe we will find out which company
No matter how good the policy, we
There is a chance to reject the claim.
So let's have a policy.
When we take, we were before
Any illnesses
Some people would say if there were
I don't have that disease now, but I used to.
We need some medicine.
Whatever you have eaten,
It should have been reported to the correct company.
Only then will you have a policy.
You can always take it.
You should have noticed this too.
Who are your friends?
You said this even though you took out a policy.
Okay, let's see the video.
Let's go to the presentation. This video clip
It's long, so you
Please pay attention and watch this video in full.
Only then will you like this video.
I understand. Okay, let's go.
Let's go to the presentation.
Hello everyone. Power Link
Another new feature on our channel
Welcome everyone to the video.
Today I want to share with you
Going to ICC Lampard's best
The new Elevate
That's the plan. Elevate
You know the meaning of the word.
Take it to the next level
Like being lifted up, that is
Close to the customer experience
A policy that takes it to the next level
ICC Lampard has called this a
Presenting the plan.
You know about the ICC Group.
India's number one in the finance sector
A company that currently exists
ICC Lampard is the company to come from
In the health industry in the coming years
A growth in the economic sector
Because everyone expects
Yes, many companies.
Health insurance with policies
Coming to the region
Accordingly, the agency in the country
Likewise, many policies
The number of customers has also increased.
The reason for this is that there is such a
One reason for the demand in the future
We spend a lot of money on healthcare.
It's just that it will cost money.
Because everyone knows
Same
The post office is just around the corner.
In many places since
We have many policies available.
It has reached the point where
Special attention should be paid to the policy
It is the customers who take it, that is.
Which policies should be selected?
Which ones suit your needs?
The policy to be selected is
Of course it is the customer's responsibility.
That's the reason for all these policies.
We have policies in many places.
Which one of these is being brought straight?
What is useful to us?
To evaluate is to evaluate the customer.
The most important thing about
Policies matter.
Every day is changing.
Each of the company's policies
Evaluate and see if it is useful for us.
What's up?
It should be evaluated and it should be absolutely
A customer's need is often
It is a difficult time for them.
It's time to make this decision.
Is
Then yours is like that
This is to clear up any doubts.
I am yours with the video.
This one has come to the fore.
To clear your doubts in the video
All things for
So you're saying this whole video.
Elevate is a must-see.
This one word for this one policy
How suitable is it?
We're going to check.
This means that the customer experience is
Policy to another level
Are we delivering today?
This video is for you to watch.
I hope it will be useful for you.
Hoping
ICC says elevate
There is a lot in this policy of Lombard.
There are attractive features
What are the special features?
After looking at this policy
What are the benefits?
We are very aware of the shortcomings.
Deep into this video discus
Will be doing
Before talking about the plan,
Good news, now on Power Link.
For those who take insurance from
You can renew your insurance and EMI
We are the ones who will do the work.
Paving the way for more information
Contact this number
Useful things like this to do
Our power link for videos
This is a video from this channel, please.
Like, share and subscribe to our channel.
Subscribe
The first thing I'm going to say is
Interested
A place that customers love.
What is special about Infinite Coverage is that we
Customers always have a policy.
A time to think about taking
It would be important to know about Sum Insured.
After you take out a policy,
You will understand a coverage
When you have to get it, that is, you
If you want a coverage, the sum insured
For example, a percentage of 10%
So something like a condition
It might be coming.
That's how we will have coverage.
Isn't it available? This is in most policies.
That's how it is. But this is an elevator.
In this policy, we have infinite
Coverage is available. That is, this one
The company has given us infinite coverage in the policy.
We have a limited amount of coverage.
The company provides. Now
Similarly, a person who has taken this policy
Individual Unlimited Same Insured Choice
Even if you don't do it, the person has a
A big claim is coming. That is now 5
Lakh or 6 lakhs taken together
A person has an accident or
Something unexpected like this
17 or a 20 for a reason
The amount of lakhs is 20 or 25 lakhs.
He has one claim and one amount.
Imagine having to pay.
If so, the life of this one policy
Listen to this once in a while.
During the lifetime of this one policy of yours
Once the company is like this, that is, this much
A huge claims company together
This is a good plus to give.
Isn't this the point of the company?
Accidental, that is, accidental.
The person's sum inshow or sub limit etc.
Nothing will be considered.
That is, an optional add-on to this policy.
This is an addon called Infinite Care.
Once in a lifetime by taking
You have yours like this.
For things like accidents
If it happens, it will happen.
Accident or something else happened.
You may be unexpectedly affected by the needs
For needs like this
The company has a big claim.
It will be given in your lifetime.
Once
Infinite sum insured as well
Infinite Care Infinite Samsha You
Note that as mentioned earlier
Infinite Sumshad and Infinite Care are included in this
This is coming. This is an additional addon.
Two very interesting ones
These optional addons are features you
It is necessary to understand in advance.
That means you have to do this in advance.
Must be added to your policy
Only then will this privilege be granted.
You will get it next.
It's a good feature to say.
Unlimited reset of sum insured
That means you have your money.
Insured for unlimited time
You can reset it.
You can claim for the same illness.
You can do it but you have the same
You can claim for illness.
Claim for the same illness by the same person
It can be done, but for the same disease.
If you claim again
You have to wait 45 days, which means
Now to the same person, to a person
Claim again for the same illness
You have to claim again later.
If you come, you will get it.
It's worth waiting 45 days but
For other family members
If you have this illness
If so, you can quickly
This is a reset that has been done.
Unlimited reset of sum via option
You have the option of being insured.
Available
Same person for the same illness
Only if you want that claim again.
You have to wait 45 days.
For example, this is a loan of Rs. 10 lakhs.
Suppose it is a claim that another person
You have another one in the family.
For an individual, i.e. a member of a family
The individual has a claim of Rs. 10 lakh.
10 lakh rupees due to illness
If you want a claim, it's up to you.
It is available but to the same person.
The same disease, the same disease again
45 days if you need to claim
It's worth waiting for, but...
This is for another person in the family.
If you get sick, wait 45 days.
This person doesn't have to do it.
That is, for a person who has already been sick
Wait 45 days even if you get another illness
In short, there's nothing to do.
One person in a family has the same
Claim again for illness
If you take it, claim it once.
Take it and claim it again
If you take it, wait 45 days.
The next feature to do is
What is the Infinite Guaranteed Bonus?
Please note this is not a no-claim bonus.
This is an Infinite Guaranteed Bonus.
That means it's guaranteed at the end of the year.
Even though it's guaranteed, 20% of your suminshow
It will be a bonus add-on. You
Whether or not the claim is taken, this
It will be a bonus. Fifth year
By then, it will be twice as much as Sumshad.
You can claim.
Along with this, another optional
Benefits provided by the company.
That's 100% of our income every year.
That it will be added to the insurance word.
That is, a sum of 10 lakhs.
To a person who has taken
When a person reaches the tenth year, his/her
It will be one crore. About two dozen
Optional benefits that come with this plan
Yes. You have a basic plan.
If only that were enough,
It is enough to pay the premium but
You also get additional benefits from this.
If you want it, then for that
Pay extra premium
You can take this one policy.
What we have been saying all this time is additional, that is
Now about optional benefits.
We will discuss through this video.
What is the coverage of this one plan?
Which treatments are suitable?
Or what are our needs?
Coverage is for needs.
Now you can say that you get
What goes first comes in this: Infatuation
Care is inpatient care for you.
As everyone knows
Coming after being admitted to the hospital
Treatment means all treatment
This is coverage for expenses.
Day care comes second.
The treatment is listed and so on.
Nothing specific is said.
This includes all day care treatment coverage.
Most of what is available now is
This is the policy in companies too.
That's right. Listed and so on
Not saying. Especially taken
Not saying. All treatments, namely
With all day care treatments
Coverage is available. Now next
Donor expenses come in third.
Means Organ Donor Expense Organ
Coverage for all donor expenses
Not getting it, but rather this organ
This one organ that is specific
For donating
For surgery and follow-up
Same for all subsequent
For all things
Coverage is available for expenses.
Next comes the pre.
Hospitalization and Post
Hospitalization, but this one is special.
Yes, up to 60 days in the remaining policies.
That means up to two months of pre-orders.
Hospitalization is coming, but this one
Up to 90 days of prepayment on the policy
Hospitalization is coming and then 180
Post for up to six months, i.e. day
Hospitalization is also coming, and that's one of them.
This is a good plus point of the policy.
That's a positive thing.
One benefit of this is that we
Now, after showing it to the OP, the doctor said
For surgery or something like that.
If we are asked to be admitted,
Before that, the rest
Things like CT scans
That is, the other doctor must have done it.
You may have seen other medicines.
Things like that
It must have been done for that very reason.
Even though it costs us a lot of money
There will be after all this.
We are admitted here after
Being a doctor now
After saying this, then this amount is ours.
We can prepay an amount that has gone out of hand.
And post-hospitalization
To reimburse
It will be possible.
It will be possible, that is, three
Up to the previous month's treatment expenses
Getting coverage is the same.
Physiotherapy after discharge
Doctors say things like
Continuously check up
It will have to come in continuous form.
There will be a need for dressing.
Things like that
Of course there will be medicines.
We will have to eat for a long time.
A survey we conducted after we were admitted
Half the cost of the surgery is here.
This amount will cost us a lot.
For reimbursement
One thing to note is that it is possible to 180
Post-hospitalization is the day
So those 180 days are coming up.
As soon as we can, we will
Hand over the documents to the company now.
Another special feature of ICC is that
ICC's not so much now, it's so much
This is available to companies in short.
Except for some companies, other companies do this
It has been brought into effect.
What is that, we are soft copies
Only the company can do it through the customer app.
Just sending it will be enough. For the agent
Just sending it will be enough. The rest
Hard copies and other originals
We have the documents in our hands.
You can put it. Soft copies only
It would be enough to send it or
Any verification?
If you want, the company itself
The rest of the agency is yours.
Come home and verify all the documents.
Doing or in the branch
Called and your
Documents Verify
Will do. ICIC Lampard also
If your claim comes in, this is how
Just do it. A benefit of this company
This is also a thing. Another one
Specialty Domiciliary Hospitalization
Is. In the coming times, the most
It is also a possibility to come
Treatment as an admission to the hospital
Instead of searching for doctors and nurses
Come to our house and let's
That treatment will be carried out.
Things are going in that direction.
Growing. This one exists, that is,
The issue of home care has increased.
It's coming, that's what domiciliary is.
This is also called hospitalization.
In all matters and in all circumstances, we
It is possible to use this
Another feature of the policy is
Major available in the market
Even in policies, 10% of the sum insured
There is a condition coming up.
The insurance company pays 10% of the premium, but
In this one policy, we have the sum insured.
We have the whole, that is, the entire percentage.
Okay, now what I'm going to say
Ayush, who is an inpatient
It's about treatment coverage.
Sorry, Ayush treatment.
Ayurveda and homeopathy are about coverage.
Non-allopathic medicine started by Siddha Unani
At the hospital for treatments
Admitted, that is, hospitalized
If it's treatments, that's all.
We can claim this
Only treatments are covered by the cancer clinic.
This includes treatments such as
Not covered as well as basic
Road is a coverage that comes under coverage.
Ambulance coverage is a good feature of this policy.
It should be said that this is a feature.
We have our entire briefcase.
Can be used as a road ambulance or other
If you look at the policies, 2000 5000
Maximum or maximum amount of rupees
A road ambulance is waiting for you.
There is a limit, but this one
Our total sum insured in the policy
We can use it as a road ambulance.
Let's get away from this situation.
That is, from one place to another
I have to go to a faraway place.
If it comes, a good amount will be taken from us.
The cost for a road ambulance is like that.
In one situation, we have this one policy.
The entire cost of the road ambulance has been used.
It's definitely possible to do it.
One positive aspect of this policy is
One feature is another feature is already ready.
I said that's Infinite.
Reset of Sum Insured Benefit
This is a feature that is already included in this feature.
An inbuilt feature is
Our sum insured is 100 sets each.
Unlimited and reset every year
It will continue to happen, but on one condition.
Coming now sum assured, that is, now
Excuse me now, Same patient.
Same disease is again a problem, that is
If you need to make a claim
There's a 45-day wait for that.
A condition that must be met
This is the only thing that comes into play.
Other competitive
This is when comparing policies.
This one thing is a negative of this policy.
Let's say it like that. But at the same time
Guaranteed Bonus Guaranteed
Cumulative bonus and many more
That's a feature that's not even in policies.
We can see in this policy
In all other policies, we have
What we see is a no-claim bonus.
But this is what comes in.
The policy comes with a cumulative bonus.
Guaranteed cumulative bonus is
So by the end of five years
Our sum insured will double, that is, 10.
The sum insured is Rs.
By the time a person is five years old,
The insured amount will increase to 20 lakhs. Now another
If you haven't taken any addons
Even if someone takes 10 lakhs, five
20 lakhs of summaries by the end of the year
It will be the one that gets the claim.
It's the same whether you do it or not.
If you claim under multiple other policies
Our share will be zero% in return.
Or the year of the claim
That is, this is the one of the year claimed.
We don't get that many conditions.
There may be, but in this one policy
It is not so, therefore it is low.
No add-ons for premium.
Even for those who don't take it, other policies
When I try to compile it, this is what happens:
A good one that is definitely decent.
The policy will be the same, the other is surrogacy.
Pregnancy
Another thing that is similar to an egg donor is
Surrogacy Pregnancy Oocyte Donor
Things like this are very rare.
Even if it's something that happens
That's the basic coverage of this one policy.
Surrogacy is included as
There's not much to say about pregnancy.
This shepherd seems to think
About celebrities doing it
The news has arrived.
So you should know about it.
I think many people know Osai.
I think you know about the donor too.
The donor is part of this IVF.
The matter is coming up.
The coverage also comes under this one policy.
Donor and Surrogacy Pregnancy
For things like this, a
The limit is coming, which means we have to
This cannot be used in its entirety.
Maximum five in one case
This is up to a lakh.
There is a limit to everything.
A benefit that I will mention next
In this period, everyone is very
A necessary benefit
It would be unnecessary like this.
Obesity due to eating junk food
Many people with obesity
Now in our society there is this one
At this time in our era,
Currently existing in society
A useful one for such people
Is this a benefit of obesity?
Bariatric surgery for those with
Surgery using the entire Samanshud
And some other things that can be done
Wellness is something that is inbuilt.
The program allows us to renew up to 30%
New premium discounts available
This is a wellness program that includes all policies.
Cardio exercise is coming.
If we do all that
Activities like Google Fit
As a tracking app
We use it in sync.
If we are doing our
Active means what we did.
We have a base of activities.
Get a discount and keep that discount
We can use it for renewal premium.
This will be possible to do.
In a policy like that, we have
You can choose a discount of up to
We were able to get a discount.
It is possible that in addition to this, this one policy
Another interesting one
The feature is when renewing the policy.
Getting a discount is a good thing.
Let's give an example. Now, our
Renewal date: August
Imagine it's in the month of July.
In the month of July, we renew
If we do, our company will
Then you will get a 2.5% discount.
Exactly a month before the date
If we renew, we can have a company.
This will give you a two and a half percent discount.
Hike comes at premium or
Premium changes as age increases
This is for those who are coming.
A useful thing to do in the first year
Even the premium amount we paid is not enough for us.
No payment is required at the renewal time.
This is a positive thing.
A great positive side of the policy
This is for those who take normal premium.
It's not an addon, it's a tool.
A built-in benefit
The same is true of the wellness program.
It is an inbuilt benefit.
About this wellness program
To walk as you say.
All those who are difficult
You will benefit financially.
To walk with understanding
Try, that is, those who cannot are sick.
It's not about sick people.
There's another problem with ordinary people.
Because it's about those who don't have it.
That means you can
Opportunities are what you get.
A financial gain for you
Knowing that there will be, you
Try to walk, this is ours.
This is not just for health, it is our health.
Not only does it protect
Our health insurance too.
What is protecting?
Try to understand.
Another aspect of this policy is
What makes these modern treatments special is
There is no sublimit in this robotic
Modern, like treatments etc.
Sublimit for treatments
Even though we have been without anything for a whole year,
We can take it now.
Trustworthy moment
To trust us the most
We are a good plan.
Now that's a good plan.
And also about our future
We need to think about the robotics of the future.
For treatment
Not just robotic treatment
Other similar modern
That's a good amount for the treatment.
It will cost then we can sublimit
Use the whole thing without any parts.
Choose a plan that can be done.
Why would it be good to do
New major in the market
Modern even in plans
Claim for all treatments
They set a limit when they do.
I'm setting one condition, nothing more.
And many other benefits too.
Discounts and all that, ICC called IL Care
This policy is available through an application from Lombard.
Can be obtained by someone who has taken
That's all included as a basic feature.
For the person who has taken this policy
This is another benefit that you get.
In addition to this, there are other optional add-ons.
What is it that is coming?
Let's see if you are a health
If we are looking at an insurance policy, we
It is with you when you take out the policy.
The policy can only be issued through the Medical Council.
Only issued after taking out the policy
New updates every month
All claim related information will be provided.
Our team is also yours in matters
There will also be a monthly EMI option.
That too in an emergency situation EMI
OP offer for all supporting policies
Optional covers mean everyone
Personally, that is, for each individual.
Optional covers that can be purchased separately
If you need anything, please
Just take that optional cover.
If you pay the additional premium
Just choose what is needed.
We don't want to do what we don't want.
This can be placed for the required add-ons.
This optional cover requires a premium payment.
We can add it in the future.
We can do the same in the future.
Let's cancel.
Can also come first in this
The addon is Infinite Cover, this is us
As mentioned earlier, one can have this one
In a lifetime of the policy i.e.
Only once in the lifetime of the policy
Full amount covered
It will be done. For some insured
This policy provides a lump sum up to the above amount.
Only once in a lifetime cover
It will be done.
Coming in second is Unlimited Sum.
Insured this is our sum Insured this is sum
This does not come within the insured limit.
So this policy will be unlimited.
A person who intends to take
This is a sum assured premium to be paid.
If you take out unlimited sum insured
This is an add-on, that is, this is an add-on.
If you take it, its premium will increase.
This unlimited amount must be added and paid.
The inshore part you have taken.
At a premium when compiled
There is only a slight difference.
If so, you are unlimited.
Choose Samansh himself. So
It would be better to do it.
Power is an optional cover that comes next.
It's called a booster. This power booster
We said earlier that
The cumulative bonus is the same, that is
We said it was infinite.
Our bonus is cumulative.
Didn't you say it would continue to happen?
That's what this power booster is called.
Saying. With our sum insured
100% each year, these are the ones that
Cumulative bonus add
It will continue to be. Our message
With that, that's not all, we already
We have already said it.
20% bonus already built in
We are getting it. Along with this
After taking one more addon, totally
We get a 120% bonus every
20% per year and in the first five years alone
It will be complete. And that
Restore only as it decreases.
It's okay. It will only be restored.
But this is cumulative.
It will be the same. Tenth
By the end of the year, we will have one crore
I will get it. This is another 20% bonus.
It's been ten years since I've been here.
Even before that, in the ninetieth year
We will get one crore rupees.
After that our Saminshod is unlimited
As it is, cumulative.
Just like that
Will be going.
Unlimited Samishord Choose and Choose
For someone who did this, it's a choice.
He doesn't need to do anything, he's Infinite.
There is no need to choose care.
There is no need for both.
The next one is an addon
Domestic air ambulance is a service that, among other things,
This is also built into the policies.
This is a coming feature, so we
I should have added that too.
It's already there, you have to take the premium.
It's the same thing in the existing policy.
But that is not the case with this policy, i.e.
Domestic air ambulance is a
It's an additional add-on, so we
Only if we take it.
It will be enough to pay its premium.
Next comes the jump start.
This is what I told you earlier.
As mentioned, infinite benefit means
There were five benefits mentioned.
This one option is called 30.
After the day, we have our
Sick leave is available for 30 days.
As soon as possible, we will have our
Coverage for pre-existing diseases
The next one is available.
Dependent Accommodation is an add-on.
What is the benefit of this?
Standing with the patient
Accommodation for the individual
Costs are, that is, in other policies
In the Civil
With patients in the ICU and beyond
Accommodation for standing bystanders
He won't get coverage like that.
Did you get a room somewhere else?
Or at the hospital itself
Or in some other places like that
They will have to stay then.
That would be a difficult thing.
But in this one policy, it is necessary for that.
This is a product that comes with the required coverage.
Add-on is what you need.
Can be taken per day, thousand rupees
Accommodation is available.
Buy standard for expenses
Another optional one will be available.
Claim protector is the coverage.
To claim non-medical expenses
This is an option for all
Health insurance companies and medical
Expenses are covered by non
Medical expenses are covered.
I won't do it anymore. If you want to cover it, either
It has additional features built-in.
The premium will come or we will
Optionally, you have to choose
That means you will have to add most of them.
Optionally added to policies
This policy is also being done.
Similarly, this is an optional
The feature is that it does not require major surgery.
If there are treatments, it is now 5.
It will come up to %, that is, one lakh rupees.
If 5000
To be taken out of our hands
Upcoming major surgery, such as heart surgery
If so, that's a pretty good amount.
We will have to pay a year and a half.
When a claim of lakhs of rupees comes,
When it comes, we don't have money.
Non-medical will become medical
Inclusion in items
Consumables come first.
That is, the usual mask bed
Things like caps then
What comes is disposable, that is, a syringe.
Including syringes like
Things are called disposables.
So this is a claim
I took this one option called Protector.
After that, we have extra non-medical
Cost and such things
I need to get some tension out of it.
Not coming. After taking this, that one
This is the essence of the matter.
Will include. This will be covered.
Next up is an optional coverage.
What is a room modifier? We said earlier
That means the basic coverage mentioned earlier is okay.
It was, but there was one thing about it.
It says we select the room category.
What can be done with a single private AC?
That one basic thing was just the room.
Coverage is what we have so far.
All I could do was give us a room.
I couldn't choose, but this
Take this one option called Room Modifier.
Then we can get out of it.
To select up to an option
It is not only possible for us
To reduce premiums
This is referred to as shared accommodation.
It is also possible to reduce
Even if you only take basic coverage now
If the premium is high, this one
Let's take shared accommodation
You can reduce it even more now.
The main thing to note is this one
Mainly in the case
One thing to note
You went to the hospital.
All you need to do is share accommodation.
This is because you have to choose.
We have a helpful article like this.
This will only come as a benefit.
Which room can we have after we take it?
You can choose any room rent.
Nothing about such things.
There's no need to stress.
That doesn't seem like a problem, suit.
You have such a room.
You can choose any room.
There are many majors that can be done.
Room when going to hospitals
Availability is a problem.
In such a situation, this is an option
If we don't take it, our
The claimed amount is then ours.
The entire amount in your hand
The money is also going to leave our hands.
It is possible.
This is good for the patient anyway.
Choose this option for bystanders too.
It would be good for you to do so.
A corresponding comfort
You will just get
Your budget has been compiled.
Look and it's inside.
If you are standing
Of course you can use this option.
Be careful when taking it.
An important addon coming soon
Maternity leave is an option.
Everyone needs it.
They don't come, only those who want to choose.
It would be enough to do this as an additional
Premium is coming, two years of waiting
Period is coming, up to one lakh rupees
We can claim.
Another one that comes up is Newborn.
Baby coverage is optional.
Let's add it as a benefit.
This is for those who take out newborn baby coverage
Covered from day one
How much does maternity coverage cost?
It comes with its double, that is
If the maternity coverage is one lakh
This comes to two lakhs.
This is good for both mother and child.
This is a maternity benefit.
As a policy, I never
I wouldn't recommend this because one of these
There is a negative because maternity
The premium that is not set
There is a good difference between premium and
The amount coming in is between those two amounts.
Maternity is making a big difference.
Rate at the set premium
Power link will be more now
From the Insurance Division to you
A brand new insurance offer Health
Insurance Life insurance or not
Any general insurance with us
By taking you and our
You become a partner, so you too can have a
Generate income and thereby increase your
EMI for insurance renewal
Can also be used for closing. You
That's all there is to do. Your
Any relatives or friends
When we need to take out insurance, we
Give me the lead. That way you get
Points become income. 3% to 20%
You can also get income through this.
For more details contact Power Link
Number 9495Dawasa1
[Music]
In many other policies on the market
There is maternity coverage, including day one.
From now on without sublimit
For children, i.e. newborn babies
There is coverage available and in this
Coming up is another pre and post
Hospitalization and the rest
No delivery costs.
Only covered for 90 days
Newborn only up to 90 days
Only coverage for babies is available.
After that, the rest of the benefits
If you want to get it, add your child to this policy.
It will have to be done.
That's why this is one of them.
I said the negative side.
Next up is Compassionate.
This optional coverage called Visit was previously
I heard about it on Star Health and was familiar with it.
A benefit that was
It is optional coverage, meaning it includes
The lack of means star
All the shortcomings in health
They are revising this policy.
My one is taken.
Comment
The person who sees the patient
For the person, that is, flight expenses etc.
Rs. 20 per year, that is, in a year
You can get the patient up to
To see, that is, a compassionate
Flight ticket for a visit
The charge is up to 20 rupees.
You will get the maximum in a year.
That's all you get, next optional.
Coverage is nursing at home.
Saying you are a 40 or a
If you are over 50 years old, this
It would be good to take it because I
As mentioned earlier, domiciliary
Hospitalization
Currently doing well
It's coming just like that.
Another condition, not only that, but another
We can also come to the condition because we
Went to the hospital and was discharged.
After that, let's stroke.
Any similar illnesses
And then we have such a situation.
There is a possibility that it will happen.
A place that's good for walking and stuff like that.
The situation may not be ours.
In such a situation, we have a
The home nurse will have to be stopped.
Medication injection etc.
We need a nurse for things.
It will be necessary to assist.
Expenses will be covered in this per day.
That means we have 2000 rupees a day.
You will get it like this per day for so many days.
A small one is available for Rs. 2000.
Once the premium is paid, this will be a
You can choose this as an addon.
Elderly people to the hospital
When you go and come back, that is
Those who return are bedridden like this.
Will be in mint condition.
So, taking an addon
Premium would be good anyway.
No such premium.
You may not be able to choose.
Can be done as I said 40 50
If you are over the age of 18, that is an age limit.
If you are coming, you can take this.
Next up is durable medical.
Equipment coverage was mentioned earlier.
Non-medical expenses coverage in it
There are a few things that are not included.
That's the stretcher walking stick.
Equipment accidents like this
After everything is done, it will look like this
We need the help of equipment.
It will come when needed.
Even if it is for rent to take
Otherwise, we can take it.
A good amount of money from our hands
In such a situation, it may be expensive.
Durable Medical Equipment Coverage
Taking this one option
An optional coverage would be nice next time.
What is the Convalescence Benefit?
Let's say hospital cash, what is this?
If we assume that we have an accident
Something like that
We have to do our job in the situation.
If you are at a loss, that is.
We can't go to work.
If the situation allows
If we have no income, we
This is how we get some money.
This is a good coverage for that, but
There is a condition for this, what is it?
If we leave it, at least for a few days.
Must be admitted to hospital
If so, then one per year
We can claim up to Rs. 2000 per year.
How much can this be done?
I found it to be a useful addon.
It doesn't seem like this is an addon for those who don't need it.
Just choose and the next one will come.
Health Checkup is an addon.
And this seemed positive.
That's a benefit, that's the network.
Advantage is what ICC says
Coming into Lampard's network
We can go cashless in hospitals.
To make payment arrangements
It is possible, but you can
Network, that is, the ICC network
Try to go to the hospital itself.
If you are going to the hospital,
One just company for two days
At least before, that is, two days before leaving.
At least one day before
Try calling next.
Premium discount is an option that comes
That means we get a premium of up to 10%.
You will receive a discount.
But at the same time, our network
If you are not going to the hospital
So there is a 20% co-payment.
You can get this premium discount
To get it, you need to be close to
ICC Lampard's network
Try to go to the hospital itself.
But only you can have this one.
The benefit will come in handy.
Today, the health of any company
Even after taking out an insurance policy, 25
Percentage of claims rejected
When taking out a policy
Your entire family history is a
With the help of a doctor
After checking, you can
Only suitable policy plan
Choose so that your
Your health insurance policy
100 percent guaranteed
The value of the money you pay
To ensure that we
I am with you.
A better option than room modification
This is the next personal thing.
Accidental Coverage and Critical Illness
Coverage but even though there is both
I'm saying this is a term insurance.
Even if you have both, it's a term insurance.
It would be better to take
Now, in the future, critical illness etc.
More likely to be flu-like
So I suggest
A policy of critical illness
The ICC's criticism is that it should be taken.
Taking out a policy called Shield
It would be good.
Even if this option is available in this policy
I won't say you should take it because
After all this, I became independent.
It would be better to take one.
There are many conditions in this, because of this one.
There are many conditions in the policy.
Only limited editions are covered.
Just do it.
Next up is Beefit.
This option is for OP coverage only.
This is an option offered by the company.
OP in most upcoming policies
Coverage is likely to come.
Because you are taking this.
It would be good anyway.
The reason is that we have one like this.
After taking it, I called the company.
It is enough to inform the company itself.
We will be involved in this with the company.
Calling out, "Ah, one of their doctors."
Or maybe a hospital?
It will be attached. So
That way we have OP coverage.
Available. Until then
Nurses and doctors came to the house.
We need medicine and treatment.
I will do everything. Next option
It is a teleconsultation. Which one is it for us?
Audio or video for any illness
Telecommunications are possible.
This way. That too is unlimited.
We can do this for unlimited time.
You can opt out. Next
We have a positive coming.
Maternity coverage for two years
Can be reduced from one year
But that's an additional premium.
Those who need this will have to give it.
It is enough to take only the next one.
Voluntary co-payment premium
Let's choose this to reduce
Let's do it every year.
We don't have a premium for that.
No need to claim anymore.
That is, if there is a higher premium, etc.
This is an option for all the elderly.
You will be better off choosing.
If you are an NRI, for a period of five years.
But I won't come home.
If that's the case, you
It would be nice to take payment.
If you only pay its premium
That's enough, not only for its shepherd.
There was a problem.
Co-payment only if possible
You will only need to pay the rest.
After you come home, this company
The payment is called a co-payment.
If you can settle everything
10% to 50% of the cost will be enough.
Payment options
Coming. Along with this, a
Let me tell you one more thing. This health insurance
That someone else brought us
It's not something to be taken lightly. We
What we understand is that we are our
Understand the situations and things
We choose one ourselves.
I will have to take it. Which one should we have?
Is the policy appropriate? Research it.
That would be if we discovered it ourselves.
The best. Someone else's
Influenza and so on
For your needs without delay
There must be an appropriate policy.
What to take. We have a good civil
If we have a score, we can get a loan.
Isn't that how we feel now?
If you have a civil score, you can get health insurance.
You will also get discounts. This ICC
Lampard's Elevate plan
ICC Lampard's other
Good discounts on plans too
Available. 750 is above.
If our civil score is
Up to 15% discount on premium
Coming. This is available every year.
Now you are the highest sum insured.
A good premium considering I had to take it.
Thinking it would be worth it
If you don't take it, you
If you have a good civil score
Of course you can take it. 15%
You will get a discount of up to . That much
At a low premium that is not too high
This is possible. This is ICC
Only Lombard's positive
It's a thing. This is what this policy is all about.
Important reasons to take.
That is, the positive aspects.
As mentioned earlier, we are renewing
That is, the premium renewal premium
Up to two and a half percent if paid early
We will get a discount. Seven and a half percent.
15% is divided into two categories:
Related to civil score
Discount coming. Taking a policy
Our name and phone number right on time.
After we give everything, we can
I understand. A separate PAN card for that.
No need for an Aadhaar card or anything like that.
Are you planning to take this policy?
If so, of course you
I specifically asked the agent if I wanted this too.
Just say so and take the policy. Now
What I'm going to say is that besides this
Other discounts on the policy
It's about. As mentioned earlier, wellness
Discount 30% discount available
That means the wellness discount is 30%.
Then comes the Early Early Renewal.
2.5%
Getting a discount is nothing.
Another additional discount is
Long term is also used in many other policies.
This is a discount.
Second year premium on all policies
That is, 7.F in the second year.
There will be a discount.
15% discount on the third year
Up to 10% on some upcoming policies
Only the discount is visible, but this
The policy, that is, this ICC Lombard
What is special about this policy called Elevate?
10% discount in the second year itself
What you get is 15% in the third year.
If so, we get this third
If we look at an average over the year,
We have a premium discount of 8 to 10%.
We are now getting a three-year policy.
I don't plan to take it.
You plan to take a three-year policy.
Not doing one year policy
Even though there is funding, it takes three years.
Take the plan and then EMA within it
If we want to put EMA, we need to start from 12 months.
We offer a premium period of up to 18 months.
You can get it and close it as a monthly EMA.
Monthly premium will be enough to pay.
When it's done, the fish will be ready.
Additional interest may accrue when you pay.
If possible, then total
It's been three years.
We will pay 25% of the premium first.
We will have to pay later, so we will have to wait for the EMA.
Then we can close this
When we take three years together, we can
The discount interest you get there
It's going to be a no-cost EMA.
So we have a three-year policy.
This one of the three years can be taken
EMA we are the first year
Once it's closed, we'll have tension again.
You can stay free for the second year too.
About the third year and then the renewal
I don't need to think anymore.
We are
In the fourth year
Just renew. That is, it is like this.
It is taken in three years.
If so, we have a good benefit.
We will get it. This
It's been three years since the renewal.
When we take it away, we get an EMI like this
You can choose. And the wellness benefit
If there is 30%, we can claim that too.
Can do 2.5%
That's a nuke claim too.
Renewal is possible.
2.5% for premium
Let's claim this.
We will have a balance after looking at it.
Now we are going to tell you what to put in the EMA.
Who can join this policy?
This policy entry means "it is possible".
Age means a
As individuals, we have this
You must be 18 years of age to join the policy.
It has to be perfect because this is legal.
Contract is supreme for us.
Even to bring it to court and file it
It is a legal contract that can be enforced.
Our policy document is all about
A policy document is a legal contract.
So you took out a policy.
If it is a card, then it means
The card you receive is a legal one.
Your policy is not a document.
The agent was asked for the document itself.
Buy it, that will be the legal document.
You say card
Easy to use
One is then the entry age comes into it.
I'm 18 years old but there's an age limit for this.
Nothing, we can do this until any age.
18 is the age to be a member of the policy.
Since the age of 18, that is, I
What we mean is that after the age of 18, we
In the policy until any age
It is possible to be a member. Now a
Until the age of 60, 70 or 80
Even if we are fresh in this policy,
You can join as.
A premium will be accordingly
There is only one thing. Our Age
As our health increases
It would be bad. Accordingly, we have
The premium will also be higher. Risk
That's why it will be more
The premium will also be higher on the policy.
At least 25% of annual income
Try to postpone. Keep all that.
Things to see and do. Because
Pension will be the main thing.
That is called income. Then in it
Set aside 25% from
When we say it, we mean it correctly.
Calculate and budget
Set aside. As said earlier
Unlimited from Rs. 5 lakh onwards
Sum insured comes as. Three
We can choose from a sum of up to a crore.
It can be done. From it
Sum insured plan for those above
It would be good to choose. This
In the policy, we have Husband Wife and
To include up to three children
Can. A fourth child
If yes, then two with the husband.
Children: Two children with wife
Only then can the policy be split.
It can only be taken. Likewise
Elderly parents are covered under this policy.
Cannot be included. For them too
Separately.
I will have to take it. Likewise
Having become dependent on the old plan
For the child who comes, i.e. dependent
Child only up to 25 years of age
It could have been. But now
This is the same as in many other plans.
30 per dependent child in the plan
Allowed up to age. Now
What I am going to say is the most important thing.
It's a thing. That's how to get a claim.
How long will we have to wait?
That is. Waiting period
What I'm going to talk about. ICC
Initials in this one policy of Lombard
The waiting period is up to 30 days.
Accidental accident means that in an accident,
Waiting period does not apply. Apart from that
If you have other illnesses, this is a waiting period.
Period applies. Next Pre
Waiting time for existing disease
It's period. Before taking out a policy
Up to and including illness or accident
All the surgeries we have done are pre-
As an existing disease
Calculated. If it's like this
The jump start we mentioned earlier
If we don't choose our option,
Waiting period of up to 36 months
It is coming. That is, the fourth renewal.
We can only do this after paying the premium.
The claim will be received. Now to say
Going to specific illness
There is a waiting period. Specific
List of 14 illnesses
Done. The wait time is two years.
My period is coming. Next is bariatric
Surgery and a 24-month waiting period
Yes. That is, the premium in the third year
Once closed, we can claim.
Okay. What I am going to say now is about this policy.
That's a negative after 90 days.
Only we can
Can I claim for a specific disease?
Sorry, claim for critical illness.
Now this is all that can be done.
Cardiac arrest Hypertension
Stroke is a critical illness.
This is a pre-existing disease.
Or even if we have 90 days
You will have to wait 91 days.
We have been claiming this since
What can be done?
After selecting the Start option
If we wait 30 days...
That will be enough. That is a negative of this policy.
It seems so. Now the policy has been said.
We are among those who come.
Positive and negative
Things have been said. You have this.
Clearly understood, everyone skips.
I watched this video without doing anything.
Believe. So this is a video
If you found it useful
This one channel called our Power Link
Subscribe and like the video.
And your friends and
Don't forget to share with your family.
Thank you for a health insurance policy.
If you are looking, we are with you.
Medical while taking the policy
Policy issued only through the council
All you have to do is take out the policy and
New updates every month
All claim related information will be provided.
Our team is also yours in matters
There will also be a monthly EMI option.
That too in an emergency situation EMI
OP offer for all supporting policies
[Music]